

Profile

Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Stable background in using tools like Git, Github and React.

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible and hard working person. I am a mature team worker and adaptable to all challenging situations. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. I'm an exceptional developer hoping to fine-tune my skills and achieve greater heights in my career. My growth is unparalleled and never-ending

Education

B.Tech, Federal University of Technology Owerri

NOVEMBER 2019 - APRIL 2024

Certifications

Responsive Web Design, freeCodeCamp

APRIL 2022 - MAY 2022

JavaScript Algorithm and Data Structures, freeCodeCamp

MAY 2022 - JUNE 2022

Web Development Foundations, Udacity

APRIL 2022 - MAY 2022

Experience

React JS Intern, Terra Learning (Side Hustle)

JUNE 2023 - JULY 2023

Frontend Developer Intern, StackClique (Agunwami Enterprises)

JULY 2023 - OCTOBER 2023

Soft skills

Research

Communication

Teamwork

Problem-solving

Time management

Critical thinking

Decision-making

Organizational

Adaptability

Leadership

Resourcefulness

Openness to criticism

Details

Owerri, Imo State Nigeria +2347063265056 udonsichisom02@gmail.com

Nationality NIGERIAN

Links

LinkedIn - bit.ly/chisom-linkedIn GitHub - bit.ly/chisom-git Frontend Mentor - bit.ly/chisom-fem

Skills

HTML CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

Git & GitHub

SASS

React

Tailwind

Hobbies

Coding, Watching anime, and Listening to music